typeaconference.com 2015-06-14

# Privacy Policy - Type-A Parent

Type-A Parent is committed to protecting your privacywhen you use our services (“Services”). In this policy we explain how and why we collect your information, what we do with it and what controls you have over our use of it.

From time to time, we add or change functions, features or productsto our Web Sites or add or change Services. This, and our commitment toprotecting the privacy of your personal information, may result in periodic changes to this Privacy Policy. As a result, please remember to refer back to this Privacy Policy regularly to review anyamendments.

Any questions regarding our Privacy Policy should be directed to [kelby at parent dot com](mailto:kelby@typeaparent.com).

## Your acceptance of these Privacy Statement terms

By using any of the sites within our web site network (“Web Sites”)or our Services, you unconditionally agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy.

## What data do we collect and how do we use it?

Type-A Parent collects and processes information about you in order to:

(i) identify you each time you visit a Web Site or wish to have aService provided;(ii) process orders or applications submitted by you;(iii) improve our Services and Web Sites(iv) Customize your experience, for example, provide advertisements that we think are relevant to you and which support any specific requests for information you may make through keyword searches;(v) carry out research on the demographics, interests and behavior ofall of our customers; and(vi) send you information we think you may find useful.

You may be asked, either when you register with us, or at other times, for information about yourself, such as your name, e-mail address, postal address and telephone number. You may also be asked to share with us your interests, hobbies and preferences. In addition, when you order certain goods or services from our Web Sites, we will need to know your credit/payment card number and expiration date.

You are under no obligation to provide this information, but if you don’t then we may not be able to provide you with certain services or personalize your experience and tailor our Services for you (forexample, tell you about special offers on things you’re interested in).

## Log files/IP addresses

When you visit our Web Sites, we automatically log your IP address (the unique address which identifies your computer on the internet) which is automatically recognized by our web server. We use IP addresses to help us administer our Web Sites and to collect broad demographic information for aggregate use. 

## Non personal information

We may automatically collect non-personal information about you such as the type of internet browsers you use or the site from which you linked to our Web Sites. 

We may from time to time supply the owners or operators of third party sites from which it is possible to link to our Web Sites with information relating to the number of users linking to our Web Sites from their sites. You cannot be identified from this information.

## Use of Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information that a Web Site transfers to yourhard drive to store and sometimes track information about you. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can change your browser to prevent that. However, you may not be able totake full advantage of a Web Site if you do so. Cookies are specific tothe server that created them and cannot be accessed by other servers, which means they cannot be used to track your movements around the web. Although they do identify a user’s computer, cookies do not personally identify customers or passwords. Credit card information is not stored in cookies.

## We use cookies for the following reasons:

(i) To identify who you are and to access your account information;(ii) To estimate our audience size and patterns;(iii) To ensure that you are not asked to register twice;(iv) To control how often visitors see similar ads;(v) To track preferences and to improve and update our Web Site; and(vi) To track the progress and number of entries in some of our promotions and contests.

## With whom is the information shared?

Type-A Parent will not share, sell or rent your personal information to third parties. However, we may disclose your personal information to third party suppliers who provide services on our behalf. We also share information about our event attendees and participants if they checked the opt-in box to have their information shared with sponsors. Those who check no will not have their information shared.

Type-A Parent may disclose aggregate statistics about our sales, our Web Site visitors and customers of our services in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers and other reputable third parties and for other lawful purposes, but these statistics will not include personally identifying information.

Type-A Parent may disclose personal information ifrequired to do so by law or if it believes that such action isnecessary to protect and defend the rights, property or personal safety of Type-A Parent and its Web Sites, visitors to the WebSites and customers of our Services.

Our Web Site contains links to the sites of third parties. When you visit these sites, we suggest that you read their privacy policies. Type-A Parent is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of such sites.
